Malcolm Gomes

Curriculum vitae

OVERVIEW

I am a 4th year computer science student pursuing a career in the field of software development.

I am experienced with the fundamental concepts of computer science and software engineering.

I am particularly interested in Machine Learning and its applications in different fields.

WORK EXPERIENCE

JANUARY 2019 - PRESENT

Caev

Full Stack Developer

Developing Full Stack web application for a catering platform.

Using Node.js to work on backend applications.

Using React JS to build user interfaces and interactive web pages.

Created Wireframes to design user interfaces for front web application.

SEPTEMBER 2018 - JANUARY 2019

Review Board

Front End Web Developer

Used Backbone.js and LESS to improve the user interface and user experience of the Review Board tool

Used the Jasmine framework to create JavaScript unit tests and perform test driven development (TDD). Collaborated with teams to coordinate work on a new interface for an existing web form

MAY 2018 - AUGUST 2018

Ontario Justice Technology Solutions

Web Development Assistant

Used PHP and JavaScript to develop new features for existing web applications.

Used WordPress to create and update content on internal intranet site.

Used Microsoft Word and Visio to create documentation on the use of created web applications and software.

MAY 2017 - SEPTEMBER 2017

Ontario Ministry of Finance

Library Information Management

Used PHP and JavaScript to create and update web pages on intranet site.

Created spreadsheets and macro scripts for Excel spreadsheet to automate the execution of daily tasks

Worked in a collaborative environment on a team project to optimize and improve the workflow of other colleagues in the office.

△ | www.github.com/MalcolmGomes

Available by request

□ malcolmgomes0@gmail.com

www.malcolmgomes.com

EDUCATION

2015 - 2019 Bachelor of Science

RYERSON UNIVERSITY
Major in Computer Science

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Languages Java, Python, C, C++,

JavaScript

FRONT END HTML, CSS, Bootstrap,

JavaScript, jQuery, React, Redux, Angular, Backbone,

Selenium

BACK END Node.js, Express, Django,

PHP, MySQL, MongoDB

OS GNU/Linux, Windows

DEVELOPMENT Git, GitHub, Visual Studio

LIBRARIES NumPy, SciKit-Learn,

SciKit-Image, OpenCV, Pandas, MatPlotLib, PyTorch,

Tensorflow, Anaconda

INTERESTS

Machine Learning

Deep Learning

Computer Vision

Data Mining

Software Engineering

Full Stack Web Development